(Leonard:)You're awful quiet,
everything okay?
(Sheldon:)I'm concerned about Amy.
(Sheldon:)She's acting a bit odd lately.
Oh. Well, j-just
out of curiosity,
(Howard:)what registers as odd to you?
Her behavior.
(Sheldon:)No, I have the feeling
that she's hiding something.
(Leonard:)I wouldn't worry about it.
(Leonard:)She's probably just
distracted by work.
(Sheldon:)Well, whatever it is,
it's troubling me.
(Sheldon:)And I can't eat, I can't sleep.
(Sheldon:)And don't even ask
about the consistency
(Sheldon:)of my bowel movements.
(Howard:)You heard him, guys,
don't ask.
(Sheldon:)Why would she keep
something from me, you know?
(Sheldon:)I shared my body
with that woman.
(Sheldon:)And my Netflix password.
(Sheldon:)They recommended
Stella Got Her Groove Back
(Sheldon:)because of her.
(Leonard:)Buddy, buddy, listen,
(Leonard:)nothing bad is going on,
(Leonard:)she just... she just
didn't want you to know
(Leonard:)that the work on her apartment
was finished a couple weeks ago.